Over eleven years of experience as a software engineer. Microsoft .NET oriented, but easily capable to switch to other technologies. Particularly interested in web development, distributed systems, performance, security and good design principles. Strong focus on agile process and its constant improvement. Deep understanding how to design maintainable systems and write clear, self-descriptive code. Experience working in a multinational environment. Currently working as a senior software engineer in Gdansk.

Work History

2019-08

Senior Software Engineer

- present

Spartez Software, Gdansk, Poland

https://spartez-software.com

.NET / C#, Node.js, TypeScript, Google Cloud Platform
Worked on the top company product - TFS4JIRA - a solution to
synchronize between Azure DevOps and Jira. A product
oriented company where I spent much time on design and data
analysis. Frequent direct contact with clients was also a part of
my job.

2018-02

Senior Software Engineer

- 2019-08

ABB - Library, Krakow

https://library.abb.com

.NET Core / C#, ASP.NET Web API, React, Azure, MS SQL Server, Entity Framework

Portal for searching and storing technical documentation for the whole corporation. Work equally divide between backend and frontend. Strong focus on application safety and performance. The project involved big data volumes.

2016-09

Senior Software Engineer

- 2018-02

SDC A/S - ERP Eika, Warsaw, Poland

https://www.sdc.dk

.NET / C#, ASP.NET Web API, WCF, ASP.NET MVC, Angular Implementation of the PSD2 directive. Financial institutions will be obliged to expose web interfaces for user bank account management and the system was to handle such calls in a safe and secure manner.

2015-05

Senior Software Engineer

- 2016-09

KMD Poland Sp. z o.o. - AnyPay, Warsaw, Poland

https://career.kmd.net

.NET / C#, ASP.NET Web API, Angular, MS SQL Server,

Łukasz Łepecki

Software Engineer



Personal Info

Phone

+48 798475077

Email

contact@lepecki.com

Date of birth 1985-02-17

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/llepecki

GitHub

github.com/llepecki

Website

https://lepecki.com

Skills

.NET / .NET Core / C#



JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, React



SQL, Microsoft SQL Server



Entity Framework

The core of a financial system for mobile payments in Denmark. The system w created from scratch and will become a part of the existing infrastructure. The core part was happening on the backed site but the project also involved frontend areas for internal usage.

2014-11

Senior Software Engineer

- 2015-04

Canon Ophthalmic Technologies Sp. z o.o. – OPS, Wrocław, Poland

https://www.canon-ot.com.pl

.NET / C#, WPF, WCF

A desktop application for performing ophthalmic examinations. Since it was an application used in human medicine the requirements had to be strictly followed and high reliability was required.

2013-11

Senior Software Engineer

- 2014-11

Scientific Games - DaVinci, Krakow, Poland

https://www.scientificgames.com

.NET / C#, ASP.NET, web services, MS SQL Server, NHibernate

An international project the modules of which were being created by teams from three countries. The project required tight cooperation with other teams and a lot of integration work. Most focus was on implementation of a web services that were meant for governmental institution.

2013-08

Software Engineer

- 2013-11

UBS - Strategy Centre, Krakow, Poland

https://www.ubs.com

.NET / C#, WPF

Worked on an extensive window application, used internally by traders of one the largest investment banks. Work was equally divided into implementing new features and fixing bugs.

2013-01

Software Engineer

- 2013-08

Novomatic Technologies Poland – Random Number Provider, Krakow, Poland

https://novomatic-tech.com

.NET / C#. WPF

Designed and developed main module of the system, which was responsible for generating random numbers, securing them from sniffing and modification and distributing among clients, i.e. gaming devices. Key goals were to make the module tamper-

GoF patterns, SOLID, REST, **Event Sourcing**, CQRS, UML performance and memory profilers, unit and integration testing, **TDD** Microsoft Azure, cloud Amazon AWS, Google Cloud Platform Rider, Code, Visual Studio, ReSharper Git, SVN Azure DevOps, TeamCity, Jenkins Scrum, Kanban ** project frameworks Languages Polish

English



proof and efficient.

2012-06

Software Engineer

- 2013-06

Novomatic Technologies Poland – Game Download

System, Krakow, Poland

https://novomatic-tech.com

.NET / C#, ASP.NET MVC, web services, JavaScript, MS SQL Server

Redesigned and refactored an existing system in order to make it suitable for new markets. The purpose of the system was to enable users to perform remote software installation and configuration. The work included implementing new features and a brand new web UI.

2012-06

Software Engineer

- 2013-01

Novomatic Technologies Poland – NovoVLTech, Krakow, Poland

https://novomatic-tech.com

.NET / C#, SQL Server, memory and performance profiling tools

Redesigned and developed parts of an existing system to increase scalability. The system was meant to gather data from gaming devices, process them and create statistics. The goal was to substantially increase performance so that much larger number of gaming devices could be handled.

2012-01

Software Engineer

- 2012-06

Novomatic Technologies Poland – Auto Cash Safe, Krakow, Poland

https://novomatic-tech.com

C++Builder, C (embedded), MS SQL Server

Designed and developed a new module for an existing system. The module was a proxy between a large financial system and an ATM device that could withdrawal cash. The key goal was to ensure transaction safety and restrict access to the cash inside the ATM device.

2010-01

Software Engineer

- 2012-01

Novomatic Technologies Poland – Novoware Maintenance, Krakow, Poland

https://novomatic-tech.com

C++Builder, MS SQL Server, Reporting Services, Crystal Reports

A maintenance project that involved fixing bugs and developing new features according to end users requirements. The product

A maintenance project that involved fixing bugs and	d developing
new features according to end users requirements.	The product

2009-06 Software Engineer

- 2010-01 Novomatic Technologies Poland – Novoware Automated Tests, Krakow, Poland

https://novomatic-tech.com

.NET / C#, C++, TestComplete, Autolt, JavaScript

Developed numerous tools and automated test for QA division. Applications simplified tedious UI testing and simulated real-life system overhead.

Education

2004-10	AGH University	of Science a	nd Technology in
	/ Corr ornivordity	or coloride a	na reemielegy m

- 2010-06 Krakow

https://www.agh.edu.pl

Master of Science in Automation and Control thesis: OCR Neural Network Implementation on an Embedded Device stack: C++, .NET (C#, C++/CLI), embedded

Projects

2016-10	Warsaw I	University	of Information	Technology
---------	----------	------------	----------------	------------

- 2016-12 Academic Teacher

> Invited to conduct classes about software design, i.e. object oriented programming and design patterns.

2013-06 Novomatic Technologies Poland

- 2014-01 Instructor

> Volunteered to prepare presentations and conduct classes about design patterns for my teammates.

2011-06 AGH University of Science and Technology in

- 2012-01 Krakow

Academic Teacher

Invitation from my Alma Mater to conduct series of classes about software design and agile processes.

Certificates

2012-01	Agile Development – Introduction to Kanban
2011-01	SOA – Basics of IT systems integration
2011-01	Agile Development – Introduction to Scrum
2010-01	ISTQB – Foundation Certificate in Software Testing

